[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 12]
[Waterside Pavilion for Reflections, Immortal Palace]
Luo Ning.
You damn girl!
[Luo Ning, Immortal of Xiyin Mountain]
Are you teasing me again?
Old Immortal Master.
Take a look.
This is the fragrance I specially made out of the flower buds of lily magnolia.
It can reduce cold and clear your nose.
Recently,
you were worried about my brother.
Haven't you been suffering from
wind-heat in the lungs and stuffy nose?
I made this specially for you.
Smell it. Does it smell good?
You're so filial.
Immortal Master.
Since I am so filial,
can you take me to see my brother?
I haven't seen him for years.
Not only you,
I haven't seen him for a long time too.
After all,
his promotion to immortality is more important.
We can't delay him.
That makes sense.
But I still miss my brother.
Why?
You miss him for punishing you to copy the scriptures?
But
if he can
come out soon,
I'm willing to
copy scriptures one more time.
Maybe
when he comes out of retreat,
we have to call him Immortal Luo Ge.
Brother,
when are you going to come out?
What's the point of cultivation in seclusion?
It's not as interesting as these exotic flowers and rare herbs.
Do you understand what the Immortal Master said?
No.
I don't understand.
-Junior.-Hello, Seniors
Luo Ning is so beautiful.
What's the difference
between his actions and those of animals?
I never
want to
see you again.
[Demon King of the Melody Race]
Ze Shui.
Qiuxian.
[Zhuo Qiuxian, Master of Wuxie Palace]
Ning is not injured.
It's just that an additional spiritual power
appeared in her body.
It seems
to come from a powerful weapon.
But it's mixed with a demon aura.
She couldn't bear it for the time being.
That's why she hasn't woken up.
Could it be a magic weapon that has been wandering in the demon world?
Is there such a weapon?
Yes.
Immortal Ze Shui's weapon.
Bone-Corroding Harp.
Bone-Corroding Harp?
It seems
the Bone-Corroding Harp
appeared again.
This Bone-Corroding Harp has a great healing power.
Even if the Four Seasons Monument is damaged,
we can use it to repair.
How can something from the Immortal Palace
fall into the hands of demons?
Besides, the Four Seasons Monument is about to be repaired.
We can't delay it.
I'll go to the demon world
to find the Bone-Corroding Harp,
and bring it back intact.
Thank you.
Yes.
Lu Li, what's wrong?
Nothing.
You're back.
Lu Li.
Lu Li, what's wrong?
What is this?
Why do you have these things?
Soul-Devouring Spell?
Your Soul-Devouring Spell is triggered again.
We agreed to face things together.
Why didn't you tell me you were attacked by the Soul-Devouring Spell?
Liu Shao.
He didn't want you to worry,
so he didn't tell you.
I... I'm fine.
The magic I cast for you can only suppress it for a while.
You must be severely injured repeatedly.
It's happening again.
If it spreads to the palm like this,
in three days, it will corrode your heart and soul,
your blood will flow backwards and you will die in pain.
He Na.
Don't worry.
Lu Li is also my friend.
I'll do my best.
Common restraint techniques
are no longer effective.
This time,
I can only take my water energy,
seal it in his body
and trap the spell pattern,
so that it won't spread for the time being.
But if it attacks again,
I'm afraid his body and soul will be destroyed.
There will be no cure.
This spell is so vicious.
We have to find a way to break it.
Later, I'll ask the Immortal Palace
to see if there's any other way.
Where is the Bone-Corroding Harp now?
Something happened.
A string broke.
As expected, there are traces of the weapon emerging.
Judging from the breath,
he's not a mortal.
It must be that Demon King in White.
How dare the Aquatic Demons
steal weapons from the Immortal Palace?
Now the Four Seasons Monument is unstable.
The Immortal Palace is in danger.
The Aquatic Demons got the Bone-Corroding Harp,
and kept the Moon Sword.
If the three worlds are unstable,
who
can check and balance them?
Contact Wu Yang Duke.
We need his help.
Yes.
[Wu Yang Duke's Mansion]
Lu Li said that he'll send the Moon Sword back soon.
Isn't that a good thing?
But General Xie sent someone to deliver a message
saying that he will attack the Aquatic Demons.
He asked us to cooperate.
If I'm not mistaken,
Lu Li and the others can't come back for the time being.
They should be in the hands of the King of Aquatic Demons.
Tell all the disciples
to surround Moon Washing Pond.
But no one is allowed to do anything.
Those who act without permission
will be killed without mercy.
Yes.
Lu Li.
It depends on your destiny now.
Aquatic Demons hid the weapon of the Immortal Palace behind our backs.
They have evil intentions.
If you don't return it as soon as possible,
we will send troops to the Demon Palace.
You'll have nowhere
to hide.
The people from the Immortal Palace
came for the Bone-Corroding Harp.
The people of Wu Yang Duke's Mansion
are worried about you and the Moon Sword.
Doesn't the Bone-Corroding Harp
belong to the Aquatic Demons?
Isn't this Immortal Palace overstepping too much?
To be exact,
it belonged to Immortal Ze Shui.
The death of Immortal Ze Shui
was also the pain of the Immortal Palace.
Her belongings
were naturally regarded as the property of the Immortal Palace.
I didn't expect to
get the entire Aquatic Demons in trouble because of me.
He Na.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Who would have thought
after ten thousand years,
the Bone-Corroding Harp can still cause such a big trouble.
Then return the Bone-Corroding Harp to them.
Then we can go back,
explain to the Immortal Palace
and ask them to withdraw their troops as soon as possible.
No.
What about your injury?
No matter what,
even if there is only a slight chance,
we shouldn't give up.
It's useless to send back the Bone-Corroding Harp.
The Immortal Palace won't accept
the Bone-Corroding Harp with a broken string.
They will also let the Demons pay for breaking the weapon.
But you didn't
break the weapon.
The Immortal Palace sent Xie Lingqi.
He doesn't like the Aquatic Demons.
He thinks we have evil intentions.
He won't let us off easily.
He Na.
I want to see Xie Lingqi.
I think
I might be able
to persuade Xie Lingqi.
But before that,
we have to find a way to repair the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Why is the string broken?
General Xie.
To be honest,
the harp
was retrieved by Liu Shao and me.
But this harp has been trapped in the demon world for ten thousand years.
It's very hostile.
That's why a string
broke in the battle.
Let's find the Demon King in White to seek help.
He has a way to repair the string.
I just sensed the water energy
of the Demon King in White on the Ice Rock Lake.
That's because
I borrowed some water energy from the Demon King in White
to find the trace of the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Could it be that the Demon King in White
wants to get the Bone-Corroding Harp
through you.
The Bone-Corroding Harp
is useless to them.
What do you mean?
General Xie.
You'll understand after you play it.
It won't make a sound.
What's going on?
Did you do something?
General Xie.
This Bone-Corroding Harp
is the weapon of Supreme Gods and Immortals.
We can't tamper with it.
But the fact is
only Liu Shao
can play the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Really?
Looks like we need to bring Liu Shao back to the Immortal Palace too.
Now we need
a Bone-Corroding Harp in good condition
and someone who can play it.
Please give us a few more days.
Don't make plans until the string is fixed.
Are you
pleading for
those Aquatic Demons?
General Xie.
If anything happens to the Demon King in White,
who else can repair this string?
Forget it.
I'll return the Bone-Corroding Harp
to you.
If you can't fix it,
you know
the consequence.
Let's go.
If we don't fix the Bone-Corroding Harp as soon as possible,
not only will the Immortal Palace be in trouble,
but Liu Shao also can't hold on any longer.
I told you
not to come to me
if there is nothing urgent.
The Bone-Corroding Harp was brought back to the demon world by Lu Li and Liu Shao.
Unfortunately, one string was broken.
It made the Immortal Palace join hands with the human race.
They want to harm the Aquatic Demons.
Do you think
this is important?
If the Demons are exterminated,
the Immortal Palace will be left alone.
Now, the one who came is just a general.
Aquatic Demons have a foundation for over ten thousand years.
As long as we're by the water,
or in water,
I have 100 ways to kill him.
It's just that I don't want to attract anyone else from the Immortal Palace here.
Tell me.
What can I do for you?
In order to repair the Bone-Corroding Harp,
I need Immortal Ze Shui's hair.
Who would have this in the three worlds?
After thinking about it,
it must be you.
Lu Sheng, the half demon, is experienced and knowledgeable.
Everyone in the three worlds knows it.
I've seen
this thing before.
Where?
Ten thousand years ago,
on Immortal Ze Shui's head.
Lu Li is quite annoying.
Like teacher,
like disciple.
Although we can't get the hair of Immortal Ze Shui,
when it comes to repairing the string,
there is something else that can replace it.
What is it?
The spiritual vein of the 1st Branch Demon King of the Aquatic Demons
is born flexible
and full of spiritual energy.
The Spiritual Vein of the Demon King
is your
or my spiritual vein.
It can be used
to repair the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Okay.
I see.
You may leave now.
It's lucky that the Immortal Palace
thinks my disciple is good.
Please enjoy.
Did you mean just now that
you want to wait for Liu Shao and the others to come back
and let Liu Shao
take the Bone-Corroding Harp
to the Immortal Palace alone?
If they can repair the Four Seasons Monument,
they can
stay in the Immortal Palace for cultivation?
Yes.
On the day the Four Seasons Monument was repaired,
the Duke's mansion
can choose disciples
to attend the ceremony.
Good.
I have another disciple
named Lu Li.
This person
is as talented
as Liu Shao.
I also value him very much.
If you allow Lu Li
to cultivate in the Immortal Palace
with Liu Shao...
That won't be necessary.
The Immortal Master said
to choose only Liu Shao.
From now on,
they won't be the same.
Please have some tea.
Are you crazy?
Are you really going to extract your own spiritual vein?
Fu,
I can tell
what is more important.
And I can also tell.
You're the Demon King.
You're my brother.
You are more important
than me.
Fu!
Mr. Tai.
Fu.
The hair of Ze Shui ten thousand years ago
was found by you.
It's not easy.
I hope it can really heal Liu Shao
as rumored
and relieve the crisis of our race today.
This tune is called Brahma.
It's a musical score
recorded after listening to the Brahma trees blossom.
The love of Brahma
is the most true and the purest,
and never pretends.
It can be used to cure
and warm
the pain engraved into the bones.
General Fu,
you shouldn't drink in your current condition.
Leave me alone, Mr. Tai.
You may leave now.
-Liu Shao. -Liu Shao.
Liu Shao.
The sound of the harp is working.
Her devouring wound
should be fine now.
It's just that her spiritual power is exhausted.
Really?
That's great.
Great.
After Liu Shao is recovered,
she will return to Wu Yang Duke's Mansion.
Ao Hen's been looking for her.
She must be anxious now.
You're awake.
How are you?
Do you feel better?
When I think that your Soul-Devouring Spell hasn't been lifted,
my heart aches.
It won't happen for a while.
Don't worry.
Why didn't you tell me
your master cast the Soul-Devouring Spell on you?
If I told you,
wouldn't it make you worry along with me?
I don't want you to feel sorry for me.
Now that I know, how could I not feel sorry?
It's all my fault.
Close your eyes.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
I was born with only half a heart.
Now,
I found the other half.
It's you.
A demon general
was reduced to borrowing my formation for healing.
I didn't expect
you would be so cruel to yourself.
As long as my people
can see the sun again,
and not be trapped in the water,
not to mention the spiritual vein,
I can even give my life.
I still have a lot more sights to see.
There's no time to waste.
So,
I can only borrow your formation to heal
and find more demon energy.
Fun to watch?
I've asked someone to inform Ao Hen.
Liu Shao and Lu Li
will leave the demon world in two days.
The Moon Sword is against me.
You have to keep it now.
Go back and think of a way
to see what can command it,
but not be devoured by it.
If I can command the Moon Sword,
I'll kill Ao Hen first.
In that case,
we won't have any worries.
Really?
Goodness.
You really showed up.
I...
Last time you beat me up,
I refused to accept it as final.
I've long wanted a rematch.
What about
we switch places today?
It's not dark yet.
Why are you dreaming here?
Really?
At the same time,
I also reminded my brother.
Ao Hen has been watching Liu Shao for a long time.
As long as Liu Shao leaves the demon world,
she's likely to be ambushed by Ao Hen.
Ao Hen?
This is not your lair.
The Moon Washing Pond is right next to it.
How many moves from the Demon King in White can you take?
Besides,
we're here.
Could it be that
you've set a trap
for me?
This time,
we're going to catch the rat in the hole.
You don't just want your brother
to have a fight with Ao Hen?
No way.
My dear brother has offered to help.
We must get some benefits.
So I sent someone to inform Xie Lingqi.
Ao Hen's lair
is empty.
She took a lot of vitality
and demon energy for Ao Yin.
How could the Immortal Palace miss this opportunity?
Getting rid of her now will save future troubles.
General Xie,
we didn't find Ao Yin.
So that little beast
isn't here?
Sure enough, here it is.
Yin.
You're cruel.
I want to be more cruel.
Will you help me?
Yin.
Your Majesty.
Tell me.
What happened?
Yes.
It's the Immortal Palace.
Even Young Master...
He Na.
Thank you.
Thank you for your help.
Hey.
What do you mean?
What about me? Am I not important?
Anyway,
thank you.
You're welcome.
Lu Li.
When Liu Shao returns to the Duke's Mansion,
take good care of her.
Don't worry.
You won't have an opportunity.
I hope so.
Liu Shao.
I'm leaving.
We're really lucky
to meet such a friend.
Right?
Yes, but...
Xue.
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao is back.
What about my brother?
He's waiting for you to give him drumsticks.
Brother.
Welcome back.
Looks like Fattie really loves you.
He even gave you his favorite drumsticks.
Look at them.
Give me a hug.
You...
Your hand holding the drumstick...
The Lord heard that you are back.
He's summoning everyone.
[Yu Yu Hall]
Today,
I gather you
to announce a happy event
that brought glory
to Wu Yang Duke's Mansion.
Liu Shao.
Come up.
The Lord is calling you.
I hereby announce
Liu Shao of Lingxi Yard is
smart and upright.
After selection,
now, the Immortal Palace has decided
to give her the opportunity
to cultivate in the Immortal Palace.
Liu Shao?
She's so lucky.
Liu Shao is going to the Immortal Palace.
My Lord, what's going on?
Liu Shao.
If I don't want to go, can someone else go?
It's such a good opportunity, why doesn't she want to go?
Yes.
This is decided by the Immortal Palace.
Even I
have no right to change.
If you enter the Immortal Palace,
not only can you get an opportunity to practice magic,
but also transcend the limits of the human body
and become immortal.
This is an opportunity that all disciples dream of.
You should cherish it.
But Lu Li...
Lu Li?
I have another plan for him.
Only you
can go to the Immortal Palace.
However,
I can send Lu Li
to escort you to the Immortal Palace.
In this way,
you two can take care of each other on the road.
Lu Li.
Yes.
The Moon Sword will be given to you from now on.
The future of Wu Yang Duke's Mansion
is in your hands.
Yes, My Lord.
What does this mean?
The Lord meant...
Lu Li is the next Wu Yang Duke?
Really?
Lu Li is amazing.
You know what?
When I was young, I wanted to go to the Immortal Palace
to find the immortal who accompanied me for three days.
But now,
I'd rather stay in the mortal world.
And that Bone-Corroding Harp
is useless to me now.
Just ask them
to send it to the Immortal Palace.
What do you think?
No way.
They want the person who can play the Bone-Corroding Harp
and repair the Four Seasons Monument.
How about this?
I'll send you there first.
Then I'll follow you
and play it by ear.
See if I can stay.
Stay?
Have you forgotten my background?
Liar.
Anyway,
I have to send you there first.
When you play the tune,
the Lord and the others will go to the auditorium.
I will go with them.
When that time comes,
I'll stick around shamelessly.
If I can't,
I'll stay at the foot of the Immortal Palace.
Then you can see me everyday
when you get down.
You're right.
I'll go see you every day.
If they don't let me
and kick me out,
that's exactly what I want.
My Liu Shao
is getting smarter.
My Lu Li is getting smarter
and cuter too.
All right.
It's getting late.
Go back and rest early.
I have something to ask the Lord.
I'll go back then.
Come out.
Lu Li.
You really only have Liu Shao
in your heart?
Don't you care nothing about our old love?
The fire in Pearl Pavilion
has burned all our love back then.
I didn't kill you
because of the vicious plan on the day you drew the sword.
That's the most mercy I can give you.
But that's because I love you.
It's your business who you love.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's my business who I love.
It's none of your business.
Please stay away from me.
It's disgusting.
No, I can't let go.
I can't.
I'll teach you how to let go.
Master.
Kneel!
Traitor!
I told you
not to hurt Liu Shao.
Have you ever kept my words in your heart?
It's useless.
I have two disciples.
None
can be kept.
Master.
Li.
Up to this day,
haven't you seen it clearly?
For her,
you gave up the opportunity to return as Supreme God.
But she
can enter the Immortal Palace.
After a hundred years,
she'll still be beautiful.
But you
will be old and weak,
just like a rotten wood.
Are you satisfied?
If I have tried,
and the result is the same.
I'm content.
Content?
Li,
I advised you not to fall in love with her.
Because I was worried that you would die because of her.
But now,
you have the Moon Sword.
As long as you can make up your mind
and cleave the Four Seasons Monument,
by then,
you can stay with
Liu Shao.
Master, you mean
as long as I cleave the Four Seasons Monument,
I can be with Liu Shao forever?
As long as you cleave the Four Seasons Monument,
you will be a complete God of Moonlight.
By then,
let alone Liu Shao,
no one in the three worlds
can separate you.
I’ll take Bai Feng with me.
You should
think about it.
Since you're ruthless,
why should you be sad?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You instigated Lu Li to use the Moon Sword
to break the Four Seasons Monument.
But he's just a mortal.
Once he forces his divine power to use the Moon Sword,
he will be devoured and turn into ashes.
Isn't this ruthless?
I did everything to revive the Supreme God.
It takes a price
to do great things.
I am ruthless,
but I'm not sad.
This Fritillary Bulb Paste
was made by Lu Li, right?
It's gone bad.
Why did you put it on the table
and stare at it in a daze every day?
Throw it away for me.
Why?
Sadness doesn't hinder your ruthlessness.
You still have some time
to say goodbye to your disciples.
Someone has to pay the price
for the Immortals to revive.
Li,
don't blame me.